Close close

Newsletter

Please enter your email address to be added to the Lorex mailing list. This way you can be the first to know about the best deals, new products, and upcoming events.

 Your email

Subscribe

[Customer Support](https://www.lorex.com/pages/contact) newsletter Subscribe & Save

hamburger mobile close

triangle borderless

* Products arrow right
    
    arrow left Back
    
    New Arrivals arrow bottom
    
    [
    
    4K Battery Video Doorbell (64GB)](https://www.lorex.com/products/b861-4k-battery-doorbell)[
    
    4K Spotlight Battery Wi-Fi Camera](https://www.lorex.com/products/f861asd-4k-spotlight-battery-camera)[
    
    Fusion Wireless](https://www.lorex.com/collections/fusion-wireless)[
    
    Dual Lens Security Cameras](https://www.lorex.com/collections/dual-lens-security-cameras)[
    
    4K+ 12MP Ultra HD Resolution Cameras and Systems](https://www.lorex.com/collections/4k-plus-12mp)[
    
    4K Wired Video Doorbell](https://www.lorex.com/products/b862-lorex-4k-wired-video-doorbell)[
    
    4K Wi-Fi HaLow NVR System with Outdoor Battery Cameras](https://www.lorex.com/products/4k-nvr-system-with-4-battery-operated-cameras)
    
    Wired Security Solutions arrow bottom
    
    [
    
    Shop All Wired Security Solutions](https://www.lorex.com/collections/wired-security-solutions)[
    
    Security Systems](https://www.lorex.com/collections/security-camera-systems)[
    
    Security Cameras](https://www.lorex.com/collections/security-cameras)[
    
    Security Recorders](https://www.lorex.com/collections/security-recorders)[
    
    Accessories](https://www.lorex.com/collections/accessories-security-system)
    
    Wireless Security Solutions arrow bottom
    
    [
    
    Shop All Wireless Security Solutions](https://www.lorex.com/collections/wireless-security-solutions)[
    
    Cloud Storage Cameras](https://www.lorex.com/collections/cloud-storage-cameras)[
    
    Wireless (Wi-Fi) Cameras](https://www.lorex.com/collections/wi-fi-security-cameras)[
    
    Video Doorbells](https://www.lorex.com/collections/doorbells)[
    
    Floodlight Cameras](https://www.lorex.com/collections/floodlights)[
    
    Battery-Operated Systems and Cameras](https://www.lorex.com/collections/battery-operated-security-systems)[
    
    Sensors](https://www.lorex.com/collections/sensors)[
    
    Smart Locks](https://www.lorex.com/collections/smart-locks)[
    
    Accessories](https://www.lorex.com/collections/accessories-smart-home)
    
    Fusion Security Solutions arrow bottom
    
    [
    
    Shop All Fusion Security Solutions](https://www.lorex.com/collections/the-fusion-collection)[
    
    Fusion Wireless](https://www.lorex.com/collections/fusion-wireless)[
    
    Fusion Wired & Wi-Fi](https://www.lorex.com/collections/fusion-wired-wi-fi)
    
    Video Doorbells arrow bottom
    
    [
    
    Shop All Video Doorbells](https://www.lorex.com/collections/doorbells)[
    
    1080p Wi-Fi Video Doorbell (Wired, 32GB)](https://www.lorex.com/products/b241ajd-1080p-wired-video-doorbell)[
    
    2K Wi-Fi Video Doorbell (Wired, 32GB)](https://www.lorex.com/products/2k-wi-fi-video-doorbell-with-person-detection-wired)[
    
    2K Wi-Fi Video Doorbell (Battery-Operated, 32GB)](https://www.lorex.com/products/b463ajd-2k-battery-video-doorbell)[
    
    4K Wired Video Doorbell (Wired, 32GB)](https://www.lorex.com/products/b862-lorex-4k-wired-video-doorbell)[
    
    4K Battery Video Doorbell (64GB)](https://www.lorex.com/products/b861-4k-battery-doorbell)[
    
    Wi-Fi Chimebox](https://www.lorex.com/products/acchm2-add-on-wi-fi-chime-for-lorex-video-doorbells)
    
    Cloud Storage Cameras arrow bottom
    
    [
    
    Shop All Cloud Storage Cameras](https://www.lorex.com/collections/cloud-storage-cameras)[
    
    Lorex 2K Wi-Fi Video Doorbell](https://www.lorex.com/products/2k-wi-fi-video-doorbell-with-person-detection-wired)[
    
    Lorex 4K Spotlight Battery Wi-Fi Security Camera](https://www.lorex.com/products/f861asd-4k-spotlight-battery-camera)[
    
    4K Wi-Fi Video Doorbell (Wired)](https://www.lorex.com/products/b862-lorex-4k-wired-video-doorbell)[
    
    2K Wi-Fi Video Doorbell (Wired)](https://www.lorex.com/products/2k-wi-fi-video-doorbell-with-person-detection-wired)[
    
    4K Spotlight Outdoor Wi-Fi 6 Security Camera with Smart Security Lighting](https://www.lorex.com/products/w881aad-4k-spotlight-indoor-outdoor-wi-fi-security-camera)[
    
    2K Wi-Fi Floodlight Security Camera](https://www.lorex.com/products/2k-floodlight-camera)[
    
    2K Spotlight Outdoor Wi-Fi Security Camera](https://www.lorex.com/products/w482cad-e-2k-spotlight-indoor-outdoor-wifi-camera)
    
    Other Security Solutions arrow bottom
    
    [
    
    Shop All Other Security Solutions](https://www.lorex.com/collections/other-security-solutions)[
    
    Portable Thermal Monocular Camera](https://www.lorex.com/products/thermal-monocular-camera)

* Deals arrow right
    
    arrow left Back

* Lorex Smart Home arrow right
    
    arrow left Back

* Support arrow right
    
    arrow left Back

Country (US)

Need help?

phone [Call us 1-888-425-6739](tel:+18884256739)

bi-email [sales@lorex.com](mailto:sales@lorex.com)

Follow Us

arrow left Back

arrow left Back

arrow left Back

arrow left Back

arrow left Back

arrow left Back

* [4K Spotlight Outdoor Wi-Fi 6 Security Camera with Smart Security Lighting](https://www.lorex.com/products/w881aad-4k-spotlight-indoor-outdoor-wi-fi-security-camera)

arrow left Back

 Search...

Clear close

All categories arrow bottom All categoriesAccessoriesAnalog Security CamerasAnalog Security SystemCablesCloud SubscriptionConnectorsConverterDoorbell AccessoriesDoorbellsExtend Protection PlanExtend Service ContractExtend Shipping ContractFloodlightsHard DrivesIP Security CameraIP Security CamerasIP Security SystemJunction BoxesLightbulb CameraLorex Smart Home Security CenterMicroSD CardsMounts and BracketsNVR Security SystemPoE SwitchesPower AdaptersRange ExtendersRechargeable Battery PacksSecurity DVRSecurity NVRSensorsSmart LockSolar PanelsThe Fusion CollectionWarning DecalWi-Fi Security CamerasWire-Free Security CamerasWire-Free Security Systems

search search loader

Close

Country 

 US arrow bottom

triangle borderless

Login / Signup

triangle borderless

Login to my account
-------------------

Enter your e-mail and password:

Incorrect email or password.

Login information

 Email

 Password

Login

New customer? Create your account

Lost password? [Recover password](https://www.lorex.com/account#recover-password)

Partner Portal [B2B Pricing](https://pro.lorex.com/)

Liquid error (sections/header line 494): Could not find asset snippets/recover\_customer\_password--header.liquid

Remembered your password? Back to login

Create my account
-----------------

Please fill in the information below:

Error occured.

Customer Registration

 First name

 Last name

 Email

 Password

 Email me with news and offers

I agree with the Lorex [Privacy Policy](https://www.lorex.com/policies/privacy-policy) and [Terms of use](https://www.lorex.com/policies/terms-of-service)

Create my account

Already have an account? Login here

[cart 0 close

Cart](https://www.lorex.com/cart)

  triangle borderless

You are eligible for free shipping!

big cart

Your cart is empty

    [
    
    4K Battery Video Doorbell (64GB)](https://www.lorex.com/products/b861-4k-battery-doorbell)
    
    [
    
    4K Spotlight Battery Wi-Fi Camera](https://www.lorex.com/products/f861asd-4k-spotlight-battery-camera)
    
    [
    
    Fusion Wireless
    
    Recorders that pair with Wi-Fi Cameras for 24/7 recording](https://www.lorex.com/collections/fusion-wireless)[**Shop All >**](https://www.lorex.com/collections/fusion-wireless)
    
    [
    
    Dual Lens Security Cameras](https://www.lorex.com/collections/dual-lens-security-cameras)[**Shop All >**](https://www.lorex.com/collections/dual-lens-security-cameras)
    
    [
    
    4K+ 12MP Ultra HD Resolution Cameras and Systems](https://www.lorex.com/collections/4k-plus-12mp)[**Shop All >**](https://www.lorex.com/collections/4k-plus-12mp)
    
    [
    
    4K Wired Video Doorbell](https://www.lorex.com/products/b862-lorex-4k-wired-video-doorbell)
    
    [
    
    4K Wi-Fi HaLow NVR System with Outdoor Battery Cameras](https://www.lorex.com/products/4k-nvr-system-with-4-battery-operated-cameras)
    
    [
    
    Security Systems
    
    Recorder and camera bundles](https://www.lorex.com/collections/security-camera-systems)

    [
    
    Security Cameras
    
    Add-on cameras for recorders](https://www.lorex.com/collections/security-cameras)

    [
    
    Security Recorders
    
    Hubs that connect cameras, store video, and perform system operations](https://www.lorex.com/collections/security-recorders)

    [
    
    Accessories](https://www.lorex.com/collections/accessories-security-system)

    [
    
    Cloud Storage Cameras
    
    Secure your footage with 30 Days of cloud storage, even if your camera is offline.](https://www.lorex.com/collections/cloud-storage-cameras)

    [
    
    Wireless (Wi-Fi) Cameras
    
    Easy smart home security cameras to monitor and protect](https://www.lorex.com/collections/wi-fi-security-cameras)

    [
    
    Video Doorbells
    
    Doorbells with built-in cameras and two-way audio](https://www.lorex.com/collections/doorbells)

    [
    
    Floodlight Cameras
    
    Exterior light fixtures with a camera and customizable floodlights](https://www.lorex.com/collections/floodlights)

    [
    
    Battery-Operated Systems and Cameras
    
    Rechargeable security cameras that wirelessly connect to a recorder](https://www.lorex.com/collections/battery-operated-security-systems)

    [
    
    Sensors
    
    Perfect add-on for cameras or systems](https://www.lorex.com/collections/sensors)

    [
    
    Smart Locks
    
    Keyless entry devices with smartphone connectivity](https://www.lorex.com/collections/smart-locks)

    [
    
    Accessories](https://www.lorex.com/collections/accessories-smart-home)

    [
    
    Fusion Wireless
    
    Recorders that pair with Wi-Fi Cameras for 24/7 recording](https://www.lorex.com/collections/fusion-wireless)[**Shop All >**](https://www.lorex.com/collections/fusion-wireless)
    
    [
    
    Fusion Wired & Wi-Fi
    
    Recorders that combine Wired and Wi-Fi cameras](https://www.lorex.com/collections/fusion-wired-wi-fi)[**Shop All >**](https://www.lorex.com/collections/fusion-wired-wi-fi)
    
    [
    
    1080p Wi-Fi Video Doorbell (Wired, 32GB)](https://www.lorex.com/products/b241ajd-1080p-wired-video-doorbell)
    
    [
    
    2K Wi-Fi Video Doorbell (Wired, 32GB)](https://www.lorex.com/products/2k-wi-fi-video-doorbell-with-person-detection-wired)
    
    [
    
    2K Wi-Fi Video Doorbell (Battery-Operated, 32GB)](https://www.lorex.com/products/b463ajd-2k-battery-video-doorbell)
    
    [
    
    4K Wired Video Doorbell (Wired, 32GB)](https://www.lorex.com/products/b862-lorex-4k-wired-video-doorbell)
    
    [
    
    4K Battery Video Doorbell (64GB)](https://www.lorex.com/products/b861-4k-battery-doorbell)
    
    [
    
    Wi-Fi Chimebox](https://www.lorex.com/products/acchm2-add-on-wi-fi-chime-for-lorex-video-doorbells)
    
    [
    
    Lorex 2K Wi-Fi Video Doorbell](https://www.lorex.com/products/2k-wi-fi-video-doorbell-with-person-detection-wired)
    
    [
    
    Lorex 4K Spotlight Battery Wi-Fi Security Camera](https://www.lorex.com/products/f861asd-4k-spotlight-battery-camera)
    
    [
    
    4K Wi-Fi Video Doorbell (Wired)](https://www.lorex.com/products/b862-lorex-4k-wired-video-doorbell)
    
    [
    
    2K Wi-Fi Video Doorbell (Wired)](https://www.lorex.com/products/2k-wi-fi-video-doorbell-with-person-detection-wired)
    
    [
    
    4K Spotlight Outdoor Wi-Fi 6 Security Camera with Smart Security Lighting](https://www.lorex.com/products/w881aad-4k-spotlight-indoor-outdoor-wi-fi-security-camera)
    
    [
    
    2K Wi-Fi Floodlight Security Camera](https://www.lorex.com/products/2k-floodlight-camera)
    
    [
    
    2K Spotlight Outdoor Wi-Fi Security Camera](https://www.lorex.com/products/w482cad-e-2k-spotlight-indoor-outdoor-wifi-camera)
    
    [
    
    Portable Thermal Monocular Camera](https://www.lorex.com/products/thermal-monocular-camera)
    
    Find the security solution that best fits your lifestyle.

    Customize your security solution based on your needs.

* Lorex for Business tail right

Privacy policy
==============

Lorex Website and Product Privacy Policy
========================================

**ENGLISH | [FRENCH](https://www.lorex.com/pages/privacy-policy-fr) | [SPANISH](https://www.lorex.com/pages/privacy-policy-sp)**

Effective: October 11, 2023

Lorex Technology Inc. and its affiliates, including Lorex Corporation and Lorex Technology UK Limited (“Lorex”) respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”).

This Privacy Policy demonstrates our commitment to protecting the privacy of your information, as described below. Providing exceptional services involves collecting, using, and sharing Personal Information about individuals. This Privacy Policy outlines how we collect, use, maintain, protect, and share your Personal Information.

1.0 SCOPE
---------

This Privacy Policy describes the type of Personal Information you provide to us or that we collect from you when you use our Websites, Products (including all Lorex devices), Lorex Cloud Storage Plans, Customer and Technical Support (“Services”), Apps, and Cloud Services.

This Privacy Policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide to us when you:

* Use our websites, including, without limitation, [https://www.lorex.ca](https://www.lorex.ca/), [https://www.lorex.com](https://www.lorextechnology.com/), and [https://www.lorextechnology.co.uk/](https://www.lorextechnology.co.uk/) including any mobile versions of the websites and social media sites (the "Websites");
* Access your Lorex account, or use our software, products (hardware and all Lorex devices), or services such as customer support (the "Products" and "Services"), which includes the use of our mobile applications (the "Apps"). Please note that some of our services are cloud-based and certain data we collect are stored in the cloud (the "Cloud Services").

In this Privacy Policy, the Websites, Products, Services, Apps, and Cloud Services are collectively referred to as "Lorex Solutions.”

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully and check it from time to time to inform yourself of any changes. If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to [Contact Us](https://www.lorex.com/pages/contact).

### Other Links:

Our Websites and Apps may contain links to other third-party sites. When you click on one of these links, you are visiting a website operated by someone other than us, and the operator of that website has a different privacy policy. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of these third-party operators.

For this Privacy Policy, “Personal Information/Personal Data” means information about an identifiable individual (e.g. name, email address) or information that can be used to identify an individual or as further defined in applicable laws. For individuals in the UK, under the UK General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”), Personal Data does not include “aggregated” or “anonymized” information that cannot be used to personally identify you. For California residents, Personal Information, under the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”), does not include publicly available information like federal, state, or local government records, information about professional licenses, and public real estate or property records.

2.0 COLLECTION OF INFORMATION
-----------------------------

We limit the Personal Information we collect from you to what is necessary to provide you with Lorex Solutions and maintain a relationship with you. We collect information directly from you when you engage with us such as when you purchase Products from us, create an account, or seek customer support. Depending on the settings you choose on our Products, we may temporarily collect thumbnail photos of motion activities to send you notifications. We may also collect your non-precise location information if you choose to share your device location with us.

We DO NOT have access to your video and audio recordings, live video and audio streams, images, comments, and data our Products collect from their surrounding environment (motion detection and special events such as door open/close), collectively referred to as “Video Data”. Video Data is stored locally on your device unless you have subscribed to a Lorex Cloud Storage Plan. When you subscribe to a Lorex Cloud Storage Plan, we collect Video Data to provide you with the Services you have signed up for, but do not have direct access to it.

Like most websites and apps, we collect usage data which shows us how many individuals visit our Websites and, in general, how users interact with our Apps. Most of this information is anonymized and aggregated. We may also collect your Personal Information from third parties such as payment processors or third party apps, which integrate into our Products.

For the General Data Protection Regulation and the UK General Data Protection Regulation (both referred to here as “GDPR”), Lorex Technology UK Limited is the “controller” of the Personal Data you provide to us. As a Controller, we are trusted to look after and deal with your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We determine the ways and means of processing and must therefore be accountable for it.

### Information You Provide to Us

You provide information to us in various ways, including the following:

* **Account Details**. When you create an account, you provide us with profile information such as your username, password, country/region, and your contact details, such as your email address and phone number. You also provide us with information about your preferences, such as when you wish to receive notifications. \[Our lawful basis for processing this data is “Performance of a Contract”\]  

* **Purchase Information**. When you purchase from us, we typically collect your billing and shipping address, email, and telephone number, as well as the item purchased. We also collect your payment method and the last 4 digits of your credit card. We use a reputable third-party service provider to securely process your credit card-related information in accordance with Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard. \[Our lawful basis for processing this data is “Performance of a Contract”\]  

* **Technical Information**. In the course of customer support services and Product purchases, we may collect from you technical information about your Lorex Products and Services, such as the product model and serial number, software version, device ID, and device name. \[Our lawful basis for processing this data is “Legitimate Interest”\]  

* **Motion and Location Information.** We collect motion activities captured on a recording within the boundaries of your video to send you notifications about an event (i.e. motion detection). We may also collect non-precise location information if you choose to share your mobile device location with us to receive notifications when you are outside of your set boundaries (i.e. Home and Away feature). \[Our lawful basis for processing this data is “Legitimate Interest”\]  

* **Other Information**. We collect information when you communicate directly with us:  
      
    * by contacting Technical Support / Customer Service, in which case we may collect your name, email address, and phone number to verify you and be able to associate you with a service ticket issued for you. Your call may be recorded, and your online chat may be transcribed. Additionally, we use an artificial intelligence system to analyze the calls, to determine the level of customer satisfaction with our Services and train customer support agents. We may use this information for quality assurance, training, and statistical purposes so that we can maintain a high level of service quality. When you engage with our online chat feature, we may send you emails with promotions or information we think you will find relevant. We will treat all Personal Information provided during the calls or online chats in accordance with our Privacy Policy, which is designed to protect your privacy and maintain the confidentiality of your Personal Information. If you have any questions about our use or storage of your Personal Information, please contact us for more information on your options regarding the collection and use of your Personal Information during calls or online chats. You also have the right to opt out of receiving emails from us. To exercise this right, please see Your Choices and Rights \[Our lawful basis for processing information for technical support is “Contract”; our lawful basis for processing information for quality assurance, training and statistical purposes is “Legitimate Interest”\]; and
    * via social media such as through our Twitter or Facebook page, respond to surveys, participate in contests or promotions, provide product reviews and feedback, engage in a web chat, or subscribe to our newsletters. We may also collect your contact information such as your name, email address, demographic information, social media profile information, and other information you choose to share with us. \[Our lawful basis for processing this data is “Legitimate Interest”\]

### Information We Automatically Collect or Generate

* **_How You Use Lorex Solutions:_** We collect information about how you use our Products and Services, who you share access with, what devices are connected, and event data. We also collect the following:  

* **Thumbnail photo images**. We offer you the choice of using thumbnail photos and notifications. Should you choose to use them, we will collect thumbnail photos of events so that you may access those images or we can send you push notifications of events. \[Our lawful basis for processing this data is “Consent”\]  

* **Videos, audio, images**. Our Products and Services allow you to stream, view, or record video (and in some cases audio) data from your local device (Video Data). We automatically collect system logs, such as when a door was opened or closed.  
      
    If you have a Lorex Cloud Storage Plan, you can store, view, and stream video and audio data from the Lorex’s cloud servers. Video Data transmitted to our cloud servers is encrypted and compressed before transmission. \[Our lawful basis for processing this data is “Performance of a Contract”\]
  
* **We do NOT have access to Video Data when you store it locally**. If you do not have a Lorex Cloud Storage Plan, your Video Data is encrypted, stored locally in your device, and inaccessible to us. Neither we nor our service providers have direct access to your Video Data unless you disclose it to us with your explicit consent. We only use this access for the limited purpose of providing support services to you in connection with Lorex Solutions, or for such other purposes as you may authorize or designate, such as integration into Smart Home services, in which case your Video Data may be shared with the Smart Home service(s) of your choosing. References to “cloud-enabled” Lorex solutions refer to the transmission of Video Data from your recording device to your other devices. Neither Lorex nor any of its service providers, including our parent company, have access to those transmissions.  

* **We do NOT access Video Data stored in your Lorex Cloud Storage Plan**. If you have a Lorex Cloud Storage Plan, although your videos are stored on Lorex’s cloud servers, neither we nor our service providers have direct access to your Video Data unless you disclose it to us with your explicit consent. We only use this access for the limited purpose of providing support services to you in connection with Lorex Solutions, or for such other purposes as you may authorize or designate.
  
* **Device and Connection Information**: In order to provide our Services and allow Products to function as expected, we automatically collect the Device ID, Device Username, Device Name, IP Address, and Device Type from the Products you use. \[Our lawful basis for processing this data is “Legitimate Interest”\]
  
* **IP Address for Multi-Camera Lorex Cloud Storage Plans**: As Lorex Multi-Camera Cloud Storage Plans are limited to a single location for use, your IP Address is used to validate that your devices are used in accordance with your subscription terms. \[Our lawful basis for processing this data is “Legitimate Interest”\]
  
* **Website and App Usage Information**: Like most websites, when you visit our Websites, we may receive information about your visit, use or interaction with our Websites. Although most of the information we collect is anonymized and aggregated usage data, such as how many individuals visited our Websites, peak hours of visits, the general location of your device, and which page(s) were viewed, we may also collect your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address. We collect this information through the use of cookies, pixel tags and similar technologies. To learn more about how we collect this information and how you may control what information we collect please refer to our [Cookie Notice](https://www.lorex.com/pages/cookie-notice). \[Our lawful basis for processing this data is “Consent”\]

**IMPORTANT NOTICE:** Privacy, audio recording, and video surveillance laws in your jurisdiction may apply to your use of our Products and Services. You are solely responsible for ensuring that you comply with applicable laws when you use our Products and Services. For example, you may need to display a notice that alerts visitors to your home or place of business that you are using our Products or Services. Capturing, recording, or sharing video or audio content that involves other people, or capturing or retaining visitors’ facial feature information or audio, may affect their privacy rights.

### Information We Collect From Third Parties

We also collect information from third parties such as our payment processors. We collect reviews you submit on third-party platforms about our Products or Services. When you leave a review on the Lorex website, the review is made public and may be placed on other retailers’ websites that offer Lorex’s Products or Services.

We collect information about your purchases, demographic information and your social media profile information. We may also collect information about how you use other apps when you willingly connect our Products with third-party apps and products, such as Google Home or Amazon Alexa.

3.0 USE OF INFORMATION
----------------------

We primarily use your Personal Information to provide you with Lorex Solutions, manage, maintain, and improve our Products and Services, and communicate with you. We may also use your Personal Information to send you relevant marketing and promotional messages. You may opt out of receiving these messages at any time. If we intend to use your information for any other purpose, we will provide you with notice at that time and seek your consent when required to do so. We do not make use of your Video Data, whether you are on a Lorex Cloud Storage Plan or not, for any purposes other than those stated in the Privacy Policy, or that you explicitly authorize.

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us to:

* **Provide you with our Services** such as customer service and support, process and fulfill shipments, and provide the technical backend to the function of our Services and Products.  

* **Manage, maintain, improve, and develop our Lorex Solutions** such as administering the Websites and Apps, responding to inquiries and providing customer service, collecting usage information about how visitors enter and navigate our Websites, remembering visitor preferences, and using the information to improve or develop our Solutions.  

* **Communicate with you** such as sending communications or responding to you via various methods including mail, email, telephone, fax and other telecommunication channels, and provide you with notices about your account, purchases, and/or updates to our terms and policies. Also, to notify you about changes to the Lorex Solutions.  

* **Send you marketing and promotional information** such as communication about Products, Services, or events we think would be of interest to you.  

* **Conduct analysis and research** such as using anonymized and aggregated information to conduct analytics to learn about how our Products and Services are being used so that we can improve them.  

* **Detect, investigate and prevent fraud** such as illegal activities and protect our company and you from risks, threats, and fraud.  

* **Comply with applicable law** such as using your information as required in accordance with our legal obligations or as requested to do so by court order.

If we intend to use your information for any other purpose, we will provide you with notice at that time and seek your consent when required to do so by applicable law.

4.0 SHARE OF INFORMATION  

---------------------------

We share Personal Information with service providers who perform services on our behalf. We only share the information they need to be able to provide us with their services. We also require them, through contractual obligations, to have appropriate measures to protect Personal Information and limit their use of the information. We may also share your Personal Information if you requested that we do so, such as with your family or friends or with an integrated app. We will not disclose your information for any reason other than what is outlined in this Privacy Policy or as permitted by applicable law. We do not sell your Personal Information.

We share Personal Information with the following parties:

* **Parent and affiliates** to deliver you the Products and Services you order or use. We do that so we have a single, holistic view of our customers, and provide you with the best and most seamless possible experience. Lorex has implemented contractual, technical, and organizational safeguards to restrict the transfer of information. We only grant access to the personal information that is necessary for us to provide you with our service. Similar to Lorex, our parent company and affiliates do not have access to your video recordings. Please also see International Data Transfers.  

* **Contractors, service providers, and other third parties** we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep Personal Information confidential, and secure, and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them. We may use service providers for services such as delivery logistics and fulfillment, e-commerce (Shopify), cloud service providers, advertising and marketing, analytics, customer support, payment processing, financing and extended warranty, and fraud detection.  
      
    To offer you access to financing and extended warranty services, we may share your Personal Information with independent third parties during the checkout process to evaluate whether you qualify for access to their services. The third parties we use include Klarna, PayBright, and Extend. These service providers process your Personal Information in accordance with their privacy policies.  
      
    As part of our anti-fraud monitoring and prevention efforts, Lorex uses and discloses Personal Information such as your name, address, contact details, transaction data, connection data and behavioural data to our main anti-fraud service provider, Forter ([https://www.forter.com/services-privacy-policy/](https://www.forter.com/services-privacy-policy/) ). Lorex uses such Personal Information to make automated decisions to help decide whether your account is being used for fraudulent purposes. Forter may combine your Personal Information with existing information they have about you or use it independently, to prevent online transaction fraud with their other customers. The use of such databases may lead other merchants or financial institutions to make decisions as to whether or not to authorize your transaction or grant you access to a product or service, to the extent automated decision-making is permitted by law. Please note such service providers and our affiliates may be located outside the jurisdiction of your residence.  
      
    We use an anti-bot service on our Websites to check whether the data entered on our Websites, such as on a login page, has been entered by a human or by an automated program. To do this, the service analyzes the behaviour of our website visitors based on various characteristics. For the analysis, reCaptcha evaluates various information of visitors (e.g. IP address, how long the visitor has been on the website or app, mouse movements, and keypress events) to determine human confidence, as well as aggregate overall captcha completion.  
    
* **Individuals**, such as family or friends, which you choose for us to share your information with, such as access to Products through an invitation link sent by you through the App.  

* **Third party products and apps**, such as voice assistance services (e.g. Amazon Alexa or Google Assistant), if you choose to integrate our Products with those services. These services collect audio data (i.e. voice) to help operate and control enabled Products. The data these services collect to help operate our Products are governed by the privacy policies of such services, and you should review and consider such privacy policies before selecting or using these services.  

* **Buyers or other successors** in the event of a merger, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which Personal Information we hold is among the assets transferred.  

* **Government bodies and law enforcement**, to the extent they have a binding order or warrant, which compels Lorex to provide them access to your information, including but not limited to your Video Data. Please note that if you do not have a Lorex Cloud Storage Plan, we cannot disclose your Video Data and other data that is strictly stored on your Devices. If, however, you do have a Lorex Cloud Storage Plan and we receive a demand order, we will take measures to redirect the governmental body to request the Video Data from you directly, to the extent permitted by applicable laws. If we are compelled to release this information, we will give you reasonable notice to seek protective orders or other remedies, unless Lorex is legally prohibited from doing so.
  
* **Other parties if we are required to do so by law** and such disclosure is necessary for compliance with our legal obligation, including disclosure to exercise or defend a legal claim, to investigate or prevent a crime, to enforce and apply the terms of use, including billing and collection purposes, and if we believe that disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of our company, customers, or others.

If for any reason we are required or permitted by the applicable law to disclose your Personal Information to any other party, we will notify you if we are permitted to do so or we will seek your consent as required by applicable law. We may provide third parties with aggregated and anonymized statistical information and analytics about the use of our Lorex Solutions, in which case, you are not identifiable.

5.0 ADVERTISING AND ANALYTICS
-----------------------------

Like many other websites and apps, we use third parties, such as Google Analytics, to help us understand how individuals use our Websites and Apps The information collected is aggregated and we cannot identify who you are. We do collect your IP address, which in some jurisdictions is considered Personal Information.

We may also use Google and Facebook to advertise to you. We may do this through the use of cookies and similar technologies. You may opt out of receiving advertisements. See our [Cookies Notice](https://www.lorex.com/pages/cookie-notice).

We partner with third parties, such as Google and Facebook to show you advertisements about our Products and Services on websites and apps that you visit, which we think you would find relevant. These third parties may use cookies, web beacons, device identifiers, social media plugins and other technologies to collect information about your use of our Services, as well as your use of unaffiliated websites, apps, social media content, and ads to send you Lorex advertisements that are relevant to you. They may also measure the effectiveness of our ads and email marketing as well as use a third party to personalize web and email experiences for our clients.

For more information about interest-based advertising and cross-device linking practices, please visit [the Network Advertising Initiative](https://thenai.org/) ("NAI") website, [the Digital Advertising Alliance](https://youradchoices.com/) ("DAA") website, and [the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance](https://edaa.eu/) ("EIDAA") websites. You may opt-out or withdraw your consent to cookies or similar technologies either on your browser or on the cookie banner/tool on our Websites and Apps. Please see the [Cookie Notice](https://www.lorex.com/pages/cookie-notice) for more information.

We may also use third-party service providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Websites and Apps. In particular, our Websites and Apps may use Google Analytics to help track, monitor, and report traffic on our Websites and Apps. Google tracks information such as (i) your IP address; (ii) the type of web browser and operating system being used; (iii) how you navigate our Websites and Apps; and (iv) other websites you visited before visiting our Websites. Google compiles this information into aggregated statistical reports that are used by Lorex to optimize our Websites and Apps and enhance user experience. Google may also transfer this information to other third parties where they are required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. You can opt out of having your activity on Websites and Apps made available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about a visitor’s activity. For more information on Google’s privacy practices, please visit: [https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites).

6.0 HOW WE PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
--------------------------------------------

We have implemented physical, technical, and organizational safeguards to protect your personal information.

We maintain physical, technical, and organizational safeguards to protect your Personal Information from misuse, unauthorized access by our personnel, disclosure, and loss. We restrict access to Personal Information to those staff members and third parties who need to know the information to provide services necessary for us to fulfill our obligation. Despite our efforts, we cannot guarantee that information transmitted over the internet will always remain secure, which is why we encourage you to take appropriate steps to protect your information, such as creating strong passwords and not sharing your passwords with anyone.

7.0 HOW LONG WE KEEP INFORMATION
--------------------------------

We keep your information for as long as necessary to fulfil the purpose we originally collected it for or as required under applicable law.

Your Personal Information will be kept for at least as long as it is necessary to carry out the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy and subject to applicable laws. We may retain anonymized and aggregated information without time limits to the extent that we have a legitimate and lawful interest in doing so.

More specifically, we keep your Personal Information for as long as you have an account with us. Once you close your account, we will retain your information for as long as necessary to meet our legal obligations, after which we discard it. Even if we discard your Personal Information it may persist on electronic backup made in the normal course of business for an additional period of time.

If you have chosen to use the thumbnail feature, thumbnail photo images of events are encrypted and stored on the Lorex Cloud for up to 3 days before being permanently deleted. If you are on a Lorex Cloud Storage Plan, the retention of these thumbnails may be longer, and is outlined in the Lorex Cloud Storage Plan’s description. Should you cancel your Lorex Cloud Storage Plan, your Video Data will be deleted upon final expiry of the subscription.

8.0 YOUR CHOICES
----------------

You have choices when it comes to your Personal Information. Where you choose to provide us with your Personal Information, you also have the option to opt out of sharing the information with us:

* **Withdrawing Consent:** Where consent is used as the lawful basis for processing your Personal Information, you may withdraw your consent. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted before your withdrawal. If you withdraw consent, we will explain to you what, if any, consequences there may be. If you do not consent to certain uses or sharing of your personal information, we may be unable, or limited in our ability, to provide you with certain products or services.
  
* **App Features:** You have the option to opt-in to certain features of the App, which are turned off by default. Those include but are not limited to your location information, the use of your mobile device camera and microphone, and receiving push notifications, including thumbnail event photos. You may opt out of these features at any time. You also have the choice to share access to your Product by sending an invitation or revoking an invitation. These features can be found under Settings in the App or on your mobile device.
  
* **Promotional Communications:** We may send you promotional communications in accordance with applicable anti-spam laws. You may opt out of marketing communication from us either by clicking the “Unsubscribe” link on the marketing or promotional email or by contacting us at [privacy@lorex.com](mailto:privacy@lorex.com). If you opt out of receiving communications from us, you may still receive communication from us that are related to the provision of our Services to you, such as notices about Product upgrades. (If you are a resident of the EEA (EU)/UK, you will need to explicitly opt-in to receiving promotional communication as per applicable laws).
  
* **Cookies:** You may also withdraw your consent to cookies or similar technologies either on your browser or on the cookie banner on our Websites and Apps. Please note that if you opt out of cookies, it may affect the functionality of our Services. Please see the [Cookie Notice](https://www.lorex.com/pages/cookie-notice) for more information.
  
* **Account Deletion:** You have the right to delete your account at any time. Deleting the App from your mobile device will not delete your account. To delete your account, you must do so directly in the App under Settings. Alternatively, you can contact us to assist you. See [Contact Us](https://www.lorex.com/pages/contact).

9.0 YOUR RIGHTS
---------------

Depending on where you reside, applicable privacy laws may give you certain rights relating to your Personal Information and our processing of it. If you are a resident of California please refer to [Individuals Who Reside In the State of California](https://www.lorex.com/pages/ccpa-opt-out). Below is a list of rights you have that you may exercise. We must respond to your request within 30 days:

* **Right to Access and Rectification:** You have the right to access your Personal Information. You also have the right to rectify your information if it is inaccurate or incomplete. You can access and/or rectify your Personal Information directly in your account. You may also contact us to exercise your rights. See [Contact Us](https://www.lorex.com/pages/contact). We will consider and respond to all requests in accordance with applicable laws.
  
* **Right to Deletion:** You are entitled to ask us to delete or remove your Personal Data, as permitted by law. There may also be certain exceptions where we may refuse a request for deletion, for example, where Personal Data is required for compliance with the law or in connection with claims.
  
* **Right to Restriction of Processing**. You are entitled to ask us to suspend the processing of your Personal Data under certain circumstances, such as when the accuracy of your Personal Data is contested.
  
* **Right to Data Portability**. You may request your Personal Data in a structured, commonly used, and machine-readable format, which may be transmitted to a third party, either directly by us, if technically feasible, or through you.
  
* **Right to Objection**. You are entitled to object to the processing of your Personal Data, with certain exceptions, based on legitimate interests and direct marketing.

Verification Process and Required Information – Note that we may need to request additional information from you to verify your identity or understand the scope of your request. We will require you to verify the Personal Information we already have about you. You may also make a verifiable consumer request on behalf of your minor child.

Authorized Agent – To designate an authorized agent, please issue a power of attorney granting the agent the power to submit a consumer request to Lorex on your behalf, and send a copy of such power of attorney to Lorex via email to [privacy@lorex.com](mailto:privacy@lorex.com).

10.0 CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 18
---------------------------------

Our Websites and Apps are not intended for children under the age of 18 years old. While we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 18, we have no control over recordings and whether those recordings capture children.

We have no control over recordings and whether those recordings capture children under that age of 18. We also do not have access to the video recordings, however, we do store thumbnail photos for a short time, which may capture children under the age of 18. We do not readily have access to those photos.

The Websites and Apps are not intended for children under 18 years of age. No one under the age 18 should provide any Personal Information to or on our Websites or Apps. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 18 on our Websites and Apps. If you believe we have information about an individual under the age of 18 without parental or legal guardian consent, please contact us at [privacy@lorex.com](mailto:privacy@lorex.com) and we will delete the information.

11.0 INTERNATIONAL DATA TRANSFERS
---------------------------------

Lorex is a global business, which means we may need to store or transfer your personal information to a country other than the one you live in.

Lorex is a global business. To offer you Lorex Solutions we may need to store, process or transfer your Personal Information to a country, state or province other than the one you reside in. This means your Personal Information may be subject to the laws of a foreign jurisdiction including but not limited to foreign governments, courts, law enforcement and regulatory agencies. These countries may also not have the same information protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information. When we transfer your Personal Information to other countries, we will protect that information as required by law, for example, by signing Standard Contractual Clauses.

Lorex’s servers are primarily located in the United States of America for thumbnail storage, Lorex Cloud Plans, and other cloud services.

12.0 INDIVIDUALS LOCATED IN THE STATE OF CALIFORNIA
---------------------------------------------------

If you are a California resident, you may have additional rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA).

This section applies to California residents that are not a job applicant, employee, or employee of another company interacting with us in your job role. The purpose of this section is to inform California residents about our Personal Information practices and your privacy-related rights under California law, including the California Consumer Privacy Act, as amended (“CCPA”).

**Categories of Personal Information**

In the past 12 months, we collected the following categories of Personal Information for business purposes:

* **Identifiers** such as your name, email address, device identifiers;
* **Personal information categories under California Civil Code** section 1798.80 (“CCPA Information”), which includes any information that identifies, relates to, describes, or is capable of being associated with you;
* **Commercial information** such as purchase history;
* **Internet and other similar network activity** such as usage data;
* **Geolocation data** such as your device location;
* **Sensory data** such as images; and
* **Internet or electronic network activity information** such as browsing or usage data.

Please refer to our Section 2 Collection of Information for more detail about what information we collect, including the categories of sources.

**Purpose of Collecting Personal Information**

Please refer to Use of Information for details about how we use your Personal Information for business and commercial purposes.

**Categories of Third Parties With Whom We Share Personal Information**

Please refer to Share of Information for details about third parties we share your Personal Information with.

In the past 12 months, we disclosed the following categories of Personal Information for a business purpose:

* **Identifiers** such as your name, email address, device identifiers;
* **Personal information categories under California Civil Code** section 1798.80 (“CCPA Information”), which includes any information that identifies, relates to, describes, or is capable of being associated with you;
* **Commercial information** such as purchase history;
* **Internet and other similar network activity** such as usage data;
* **Geolocation data** such as your device location;
* **Sensory data** such as images; and
* **Internet or electronic network activity information** such as browsing or usage data.

**Sale of Personal Information**

Lorex allows certain companies to place tracking technologies like cookies on our Websites and Apps, which allow those companies to receive information about your activities and they may use that data to serve you more relevant ads on our Websites or others. Under the CCPA, sharing data for online advertising like this may be considered a "sale" of Personal Information.

Except for the kind of sharing as illustrated above, Lorex does not sell your Personal Information.

You always have full control over whether these technologies work on your devices. You can disable them entirely using our cookie consent preference tools, or by clicking the [Do Not Sell My Personal Information](https://www.lorex.com/pages/personal-information) link on our Websites. For more detail, please see Advertising and Analysis as well as our [Cookie Notice](https://www.lorex.com/pages/cookie-notice).

**Your Rights Regarding Personal Information**

California residents have certain rights with respect to their Personal Information collected by businesses. If you are a California resident, you may exercise the following rights regarding your Personal Information, subject to certain exceptions and limitations:

* The right to know the categories and specific Personal Information we collected, used, disclosed, and sold about you over the past 12 months and the categories of sources from which we collected your Personal Information, our purposes for collecting or selling your Personal Information, the categories of your Personal Information that we have either sold or disclosed for a business purpose and the categories of third parties with which we have shared personal information;
* The right to access and portability of Personal Information that we collected over the past 12 months. You also have the right to request we provide you with a copy of the Personal Information we collected in a portable, readily reusable format that allows you to transmit the information to a third party.
* The right to request that we delete the Personal Information we have collected from you or maintain about you. Under the CCPA, we must respond to your request within 45 days;
* The right to opt out of our sale(s) of your Personal Information. Please note that if you opt out of certain types of sales, we will be unable to provide you with the Services that rely on such sales (Note: we do not sell the Personal Information of consumers we actually know are less than 16 years of age, unless we receive affirmative authorization (the “right to opt-in”) from either the consumer who is at least 13 but not yet 16 years of age, or the parent or guardian of a consumer less than 13 years of age); and
* The right not to receive discriminatory treatment for the exercise of the privacy rights conferred by the CCPA.

If you are a California resident, to exercise your rights, please contact us using the following information and submit the requested verifying information, as described below:

* Toll free: 1-866-467-8688 (enter service code 739 to leave us a message)
* Email: [privacy@lorex.com](mailto:%20privacy@lorex.com)

**Other California Privacy Rights**

California's "Shine the Light" law (Civil Code Section § 1798.83) permits users of our Websites and Apps that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [privacy@lorex.com](mailto:%20privacy@lorex.com).

13.0 POLICY CHANGES
-------------------

We may from time to time make changes to this Privacy Policy and we encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy was last updated on October 11, 2023. We keep our Privacy Policy under regular review. We will post our up-to-date Privacy Policy on our Websites and Apps. We suggest that you review this Privacy Policy periodically as we may modify it from time to time as our Lorex Solutions evolve or as required by applicable laws. If there are material changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you, such as sending you a notification in addition to posting it on our Websites and Apps

14.0 HOW TO MAKE A PRIVACY INQUIRY/COMPLAINT
--------------------------------------------

You may contact us at any time at [privacy@lorex.com](mailto:privacy@lorex.com) with any inquiries relating to your Personal Information.

If you have any concerns about how we handle your Personal Information or if you disagree with our response to your request for exercising your rights, we would like to know so we can address your concern. Please contact our Privacy Office at [privacy@lorex.com](mailto:privacy@lorex.com).

Complaints and inquiries lodged with the Privacy Office will be responded to within ten days. You may be contacted in this time to validate your identity and/or product ownership before we can proceed with your request. In cases where we cannot comply with your request, we will offer you feedback as to the reasoning behind our decision. If a request is not fulfilled to your satisfaction, you have the right to complain to your data protection supervisory authority or privacy commissioner, as the case may be.

15.0 CONTACT US
---------------

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy and our privacy practices, please contact our privacy office at [privacy@lorex.com](mailto:privacy@lorex.com) or write to us at:

Our head office:  
250 Royal Crest Court  
Markham, Ontario  
L3R 3S1, Canada  

### Lorex Store

arrow bottom

### Security Solutions

arrow bottom

* Lorex for Business tail right

### Policies

arrow bottom

### Product Support

arrow bottom

### Let Us Help You

arrow bottom

​

​

Lorex products are designed for consumer and business use only and not for US federal governments, federally-funded projects or contractors subject to NDAA.

**© 2024 Lorex Corporation**

Amazon American Express Apple Pay Diners Club Discover Google Pay JCB Maestro Mastercard PayPal Shop Pay Union Pay Venmo Visa

×

You are now leaving Lorex.com. Would you like to continue to Lorex’s For Business website?

Continue Cancel

* Opens in a new window.
